{
    "subject": "resource/Moby_Grape",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Reprise_Records",
    "human_readable": "Moby Grape records are released by Reprise Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9686828255653381,
            "question": "Is Moby Grape signed to Reprise Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8358705639839172,
            "question": "Name a music label that has released records by Moby Grape."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154336214065552,
            "question": "What record label releases Moby Grape's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7935872673988342,
            "question": "What company releases Moby Grape albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7411379218101501,
            "question": "Which band's records are released by Reprise Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6409530639648438,
            "question": "What record label has a partnership with Moby Grape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5598011016845703,
            "question": "Who is the recording artist associated with Reprise Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5497633218765259,
            "question": "Reprise Records is known for releasing music from which band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5449351668357849,
            "question": "What is the name of the record label that distributes Moby Grape's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5404687523841858,
            "question": "Moby Grape's music is distributed by which company?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Moby Grape records are released by Reprise Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4081_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the record label that distributes Moby Grape's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4081_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Reprise Records is known for releasing music from which band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4081_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the recording artist associated with Reprise Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4081_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4081_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention that Moby Grape's records were released by Reprise Records. The documents discuss Moby Grape as a band from the 1960s and details about their album \"Moby Grape,\" but they do not provide information regarding which record label released their music."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}